uugobest.com 2010-02-26

# Free Email Address Directory:Guide to free email and others service

uugobest.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites to which you choose to link from uugobest.com so you can understand how those Web sites collect, use, and share your information. uugobest.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside uugobest.com and uugobest.com’ family of Web sites.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

uugobest.com collects and uses your personal information to operate uugobest.com Web site and deliver the services you have requested. uugobest.com also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services or opportunities available from uugobest.com and its affiliates. uugobest.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or opportunities or of potential new services that may be offered.

In the ordinary course of its operations, uugobest.com does not sell, rent, or lease its visitor or customer lists to third parties. There are occasions in which uugobest.com might undertake one of these activities, subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. uugobest.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In addition, uugobest.com may retain the services of a third party vendor to assist it as it attempts to determine whether an individual desires to be retained on uugobest.com’ mailing list or whether that individual might be better served by another service or entity. Be assured that in those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is never transferred to the third party. In addition, uugobest.com may share data with trusted partners to help it perform statistical analyses, send you e-mail or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information in any way or for any purpose except to provide these services to uugobest.com, and they are required to at all times maintain the confidentiality of your information.

uugobest.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

uugobest.com keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers or visitors visit within uugobest.com in order to determine which of uugobest.com’ services are most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within uugobest.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area and for no other purpose.

Please be advised that uugobest.com Web sites will only disclose your personal information without notice if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the uugobest.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of uugobest.com; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of uugobest.com or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

uugobest.com Web site uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can be read only by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize uugobest.com’ pages or register with uugobest.com’ site or services, a cookie helps uugobest.com recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This allows uugobest.com to deliver messages and material more specific to your needs and to simplify the process of recording your personal information, such as your billing address, shipping address, and so on. When you return to the same uugobest.com Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved so you can easily use uugobest.com’ features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the many valuable interactive features of uugobest.com’ services or Web sites you visit.

**Security of Your Personal Information**

uugobest.com makes every effort to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. uugobest.com protects the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Changes to This Statement**

uugobest.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. uugobest.com encourages you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how uugobest.com is protecting your right to privacy and your information.  

**Contact Information**

uugobest.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that uugobest.com has not adhered to this statement, please contact uugobest.com at admin@uugobest.com We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
